Tingting
Who are you?
Mr. Yan.
I'm not just a teacher.
I'm also your Sir.
You bastard!
You...
I sent Gu Ting your forged wanted poster.
She's so naive. She actually believed it.
Bastard!
Dad!
Get out of here!
Leave me behind!
What a touching father-daughter bond.
I'm so moved.
I injected her with a slow-acting poison.
She doesn't have much time left.
You'd better go save her.
Bastard! I'll kill you!
Dad!
Sir, the police are here.
Fall back!
Copy that.
Enjoy your reunion.
Move in!
Tingting.
Slow-acting poison.
Quick, to the hospital!
Xiao Lin, after him!
Yes, sir!
Be careful!
Old Gu!
Take it easy.
Hang in there!
Save Tingting.
Don't worry, Old Gu. I'll save her.
I'll take good care of her.
Save...
Tingting.
Who is the patient's family?
I am.
How are you related?
Only the next of kin can sign.
I'm her only family right now.
I'm the only one who can sign.
Please, doctor.
How is she, doctor?
Luckily, she was brought in just in time.
The poison wasn't that strong.
The patient is out of danger now.
She'll be moved to a regular ward soon.
Get ready to take care of her.
Thank you, doctor.
Dad.
You're awake, sweetie.
You scared me to death.
I'm just glad you're okay.
I'm sorry, Dad.
For making you worry about me.
You are my precious little girl.
No matter what,
I will always love you.
Give me a hug.
You're awake.
I just...
dreamed about my dad.
It's all my fault.
I got him hurt.
It's not your fault.
Stop blaming yourself.
Li Wen.
Where's my dad?
I need to apologize to him.
I shouldn't have yelled at him.
What happened to my dad?
Say something.
Answer me!
Your dad...
You're kidding, right?
What could possibly happen to my dad?
You're lying to me.
Right?
I'm going to find him.
You haven't recovered yet.
Take me to see him.
Dad.
I'm sorry.
You were rescued in time
entirely thanks to Gu Yan's efforts.
I heard Gu Ting is awake.
Yaoyao